newskarnataka.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy

The Newskarnataka.com Web-site ("Site") is maintained by:

**Karnataka, India**

**Email:** editor@newskarnataka.com

**Ph:+91-9632533977**

Any personal information identifying any visitor to the Newskarnataka.comSites or Subscriber ("Personal Information") if required is asked for explicitly in the relevant page on the Newskarnataka.com Sites. Personal Information is used to operate the Newskarnataka.com Sites, and we may occasionally inform you of new features, services, and products from the Company.

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable the Newskarnataka.com Sites to relate your use of the Newskarnataka.com Sites to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to the Newskarnataka.com Sites.

If at any time you believe the Newskarnataka.com Sites have not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail to feedback@Newskarnataka.com.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

If you have questions about this policy, please e-mail us at editor@newskarnataka.com

**1\. Feedback to Newskarnataka.com**

By submitting any ideas, feedback and/or proposals ("Feedback") to Newskarnataka.com through the Service or other means, you acknowledge and agree that: (1) Newskarnataka.com may have similar development ideas to the Feedback;  
(2) your Feedback does not contain confidential or proprietary information of you or any third party;   
(3) Newskarnataka.com is not under any obligation of confidentiality with respect to the Feedback;   
(4)Newskarnataka.com may freely use, distribute, exploit and further develop and modify Feedback for any purpose; and   
(5) you are not entitled to any compensation of any kind from Newskarnataka.com.

**2\. Social Activities and Location Sharing**

You may use features in the Service to share your location, status, and content, Materials or personal information or to interact with other users, sites and services. By using these features you agree that Newskarnataka.com may use and provide that information to other services and persons with whom you choose to interact or share this information. Users of these services and persons, such as your contacts, may see your location, status and/or personal information. In using these features you agree not to share information, Content or Material, or to link to any service or site containing information, Content or Material, that:  
(a) contains content or other material that is illegal or inappropriate;  
(b) exploits intellectual property rights without authorization or encourages users to piracy; or  
(c) contains sensitive personal data of others. Any interaction does not involve Newskarnataka.com and is solely between you and the other user(s).

**3.Availability and Technical Requirements**

The availability of Content and the Service may vary and is subject to Newskarnataka.com’s sole discretion. Newskarnataka.com expressly disclaims any representation or warranty that any particular Content or Service will be available. The Service, operations and some features may also be dependent on the network, compatibility of the devices used and the content formats supported.

To access the Service, you may need to download a specific piece of software developed by Newskarnataka.com or by another party.

Newskarnataka.com may, in its sole discretion, change, correct or discontinue the Service in whole or in part.Newskarnataka.com may disable any Content or Software contained in your Service account for any reason and remove any Content or Software and/or disable copies of any application on your device in order to protect the Service, application providers, wireless carriers over whose network you access the service or any other affected or potentially affected parties.

**4.Links to Third Party Sites and Content**

Newskarnataka.com may include access to sites and services on the Internet or preloaded clients that enable you to interact with sites and services that are owned or operated by third parties and that are not part of the Service. You must review and agree to the terms and conditions of these sites or services before using these sites or services.

Newskarnataka.com has no control over the third party content, sites or services and assumes no responsibility for services provided or material created or published on these third-party sites or services. A link to a third-party site does not imply that Newskarnataka.com endorses the site or the products or services referenced in the site.

In addition, you and other users may create content and links to content within the Service that has not otherwise been submitted to the Service. Newskarnataka.com is not responsible for this type of content or links.

**5.Advertisements**

Service may include advertisements. Advertisements may be targeted to the content or information stored on the Service, queries made through the Service, or other information.

**6.Personal Data**

The Privacy Policy and any additional privacy information made available to you govern the use of your personal data.

**7\. Limitation of Liability**

The Service is provided on “as is” and “as available” basis.Newskarnataka.com does not warrant that the Service will be uninterrupted or error or virus-free. No warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including but not limited to warranties of title, non-infringement, merchantability, or fitness for a particular purpose, is made in relation to the availability, accuracy, reliability, information or content of the Service. You expressly agree and acknowledge that the use of the Service is at your sole risk and that you may be exposed to content from various sources.

Newskarnataka.com is not liable for any direct damages caused by your use or inability to use the Service. In no case will Newskarnataka.com be liable for any indirect, incidental, punitive or consequential damages resulting from your use or inability to use the Service.

**8.Indemnification**

You agree to defend and indemnify Newskarnataka.com from and against all third party claims and all liabilities, assessments, losses, costs or damages resulting from or arising out of (i) your breach of the Terms, (ii) your infringement or violation of any intellectual property rights, other rights or privacy of a third party, or (iii) misuse of the Service by a third party where the misuse was made possible by your failure to take reasonable measures to protect your username and password against misuse.

**9.Miscellaneous**

9.1 Choice of Law

The Terms are governed by the laws of India. The Courts at Mangaluru, Karnataka, India shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute arising out of your use of the Service.

9.2 Changes in Terms

Newskarnataka.com may modify the Terms at any time without prior notice. If the Terms are changed in a material, adverse way,Newskarnataka.com will provide a separate notice advising of the change.

You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Terms. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your consent to any changes and modification. 

9.3 Intellectual Property

The Service, Content and Software are protected under the copyright laws. Newskarnataka.com claims copyrights in its Service, Content, and Software to the maximum extent of the law. Subject to the Terms, Newskarnataka.com retains all rights, titles and interests in the Service, its Content, the Software and in all other Newskarnataka.com products, software and other properties provided to you or used by you through the Service.

9.4 Assignment

Newskarnataka.com may assign its rights and obligations under these Terms to its subsidiaries, or to any company under common control with Newskarnataka.com. Additionally, Newskarnataka.com may assign its rights and obligations under these Terms to a third party in connection with a merger, acquisition, sale of assets, by operation of law or otherwise. 

9.5 Enquiry and Feedback

You may reach out to us for

**News and reports @:**  news@newskarnataka.com;

**General Enquiry @:**  contact@newskarnataka.com;

**Feedback and Editorial @:**  editor@newskarnataka.com; 

**Advertisement @:  **advt@newskarnataka.com; 

**Jobs @:**hr@spearheadpvtltd.com

**10 Newskarnataka.com’s Android Website or App**

This Privacy Policy contains important information about Your rights and obligations in regard to the use of Newskarnataka.com’s Desktop website and Mobile Android App. This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which Spearhead Media Pvt. Ltd (SMPL) the owner of the website https://www.newskarnataka.com/ (hereinafter called the website) and its corresponding mobile android Website or App available on the Google play store under the account of SMPL,(https://play.google.com/store/Website or Apps/details?id=com.bulletin.newskarnataka&hl=en) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from the users of our desktop and mobile Application (hereinafter referred to as 'You', 'Your', 'User'). 

It also applies to the desktop Website or App software / technology which is owned by Spearhead Media Pvt. Ltd. By viewing, downloading, installing, using or by registering Your profile with the website or App, You are consenting to the use, collection, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of Your information in the manner set out in this Privacy

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practises of third parties that SMPL does not own, control, or manage including but not limited to any third party websites, services, Website or Applications, or businesses ("Third Party Services"). SMPL does not take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. SMPL encourages You to carefully review the privacy policies of all Third Party Services You access. 

If You do not agree to any of the provisions of this Privacy Policy, You should not download, install and / or use the Website or App. SMPL may revise, alter, add, amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this page. By downloading, installing and/or using this Website or App, You agree to be bound by any such alteration, amendment, addition or modification.

10.1 INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT THROUGH OUR WEBSITE OR APP:

10.1.1 Personally Identifiable Information

SMPL may collect personal information that identifies you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to the information submitted during download and installation of the Website or App or in connection with registration for other activities or features offered through the Website or App. Personally identifiable Information collected may include name, mailing address, email address, phone number and demographic information such as gender, nationality, postcode and other personal information.

SMPL collects Personally Identifiable Information only if you voluntarily submit such information to us or provide access to such information by connecting to social networking sites through the Website or App for example when you use the facilities available on the Website or App or engage in certain Website or App related activities including but not limited to becoming a member or signing up for an account or linking an account through a social network including, but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, Google Plus, and LinkedIn or when corresponding with us by e-mail or phone to use any other interactive features of the Website or App.

You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, except that it may prevent You from using the Website or App, or certain features of the Website or App.

10.1.2 Non-personally Identifiable Information

SMPL may collect non-personal information about you whenever you access or interact with our Website or App or any of the related services. This includes but not limited to browser name, version, server location, device specific information such as the type of device used, users’ operating system and version, your mobile devices unique device ID, third party Website or Apps or Website or App or service that referred users to our Website or App, language preference, means of connection to our Website or App and services location information, internet service providers, IP address, technical information and other similar information about you.

10.2 HOW SMPL USES THE COLLECTED INFORMATION?

10.2.1 SMPL may collect and use Your personal information for the following purposes:

  * Your email address and password are used to identify you while logging into the Website or App. SMPL may use this information to control your access to the Website or App as well as use of the Website or App, to communicate with the you, customize your experience of using the Website or App and and/or the content of any email newsletter or other material that SMPL may send from time to time and provide information that may be useful or interesting based on the content and personally identifiable information relating to you.
  * Your email address will be used to send user information, administrative information, changes in account settings and any changes to the Website or App or updating User on new policies of SMPL. Apart from this if you choose to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive periodic emails that may relate to company news, related product or service information, etc. Email address may also be used for responding to any of the inquiries, questions, and/or any other requests made by You. If at any time You want to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, SMPL has included detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or you may contact SMPL via the Website or App.
  * SMPL may further use the collected information to analyse the use of the Website or App, and the people visiting and using the Website or App, for the purpose of improving the features of the Website or App.
  * Information provided by you help SMPL in responding to Your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. SMPL may use information in the aggregate to understand how users, as a group are using the Website or App.
  * SMPL may use the personal information provided by the User to prevent or take action against activities that are, or may be, in breach of the "SMPL User Agreement", "Terms and Conditions" and any Website or Applicable laws.

10.3 HOW SMPL PROTECTS USER'S INFORMATION

10.3.1 SMPL adopts appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Your personal information, username, password, and data stored on the Website or App. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Website or Application and its users happens over a SSL (Secure Socket Layer) secured communication channel. However, SMPL cannot guarantee the security of any information obtained through unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors that may compromise the security of user information at any time. It is important for the User to prevent unauthorized access to his/her account and personal information by limiting access to his/her device.

10.4 SHARING USER'S PERSONAL INFORMATION

10.4.1 SMPL does not sell, trade, or rent Your personally identifiable information collected by SMPL to others except as described in this Policy. SMPL may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personally identifiable information regarding visitors and users with SMPL's business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

10.4.2 At times SMPL may be required by law or litigation to disclose personal information about the users. SMPL may also disclose information about the user if SMPL determines that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance that disclosure of information is necessary. 

10.4.3 SMPL reserves the right to transfer Personal Information of users to another party as a result of merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of SMPL's assets to another party.

10.5 COOKIES

10.5.1 Whenever you access the Website or App we may place "cookies" on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes to enhance your experience or sometimes to personalize your experience. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer’s hard drive by the Website or App you visit. Cookies help us to identify information relating your activities and to retain information relating to your preferences and history on the Website or App. 

10.5.2 **Ad targeting cookies:** SMPL and/or our service providers may use advertising cookies to deliver ads that are more relevant to you and your interests. 

10.5.3 You may choose to disable cookies by turning off cookie feature on the web browser. However, by disabling this feature, some parts of the Website or App may not function properly. This may prevent You from taking full advantage of the Website or App. 

10.6 WHAT CHOICES USER HAS REGARDING THE USE OF HIS/HER INFORMATION

10.6.1 In case, if the user is receiving marketing or promotional emails from SMPL, You have the option to "opt out" of such marketing emails by following the instructions in those mails or by emailing SMPL at office@spearheadpvtltd.com If the user opts out, he/she may still receive non-promotional emails from SMPL, such as emails about his/her account or any ongoing business relations entered into by SMPL. 

10.7 CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

10.7.1 SMPL may update and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted as notification here on this link https://www.newskarnataka.com/privacy-policy. You are encouraged to periodically check this page to stay informed about changes to this Privacy Policy. You hereby acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of the modifications. If you disagree to any of the changes to the Privacy Policy, you shall refrain from using or accessing the Website or App. Your continued use of the Website or App following the posting of the revised Policy shall indicate your acceptance and acknowledgement of the changes and you will be bound by it.

10.8 YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS OF PRIVACY POLICY

10.8.1 By using this Website or App, you are signifying your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, You shall not access or use this Website or App. Your continued Access or Use of the Website or App following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed to be the acceptance of these changes by the User.

10.9 CONTACTING US

10.9.1 If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, practices of this Website or App or Your dealings with the Website or App or any of the features or any Legal Queries about the Website or App, please contact SMPL at: office@spearheadpvtltd.com
